[Music] Let's see the
complete analysis of the results that came after the market closed yesterday. Wonder, tell me. First of all, the
results that you have got, I like them madam,
sir. The
market is very good, you know, right now the market is
changing a lot, whatever
is domestic, plus anything related to commodities,
their numbers are very good, and where there
seems to be impression pressure,
those numbers are not good, so the
financial numbers sir are breaking this season,
Federal Bank, HDFC Bank had done a great job, the way the
numbers came, I think
if you look at yesterday also, Campaign Homes,
Kurti, I think good numbers of numbers are coming
from dear, and sir, the numbers that I think
you are seeing after some five years are
good, especially in
Spandana, so there has been a lot of write-off, all those
things are there, and anywhere any company that has to do
with commodities,
like Maharashtra or
General Drilling, their numbers are going down,
whether that form, we have always seen
their numbers are good, and what is bad,
all the cement companies sir, as
you must have seen, Shri Cement  X
happened, Heidelberg happened, the numbers were good, I like the
campaign homes numbers, in this,
my point is that there is no bad news there, so
you know this company is going away due to crisis, right now
₹500, if there was confusion among the people
or why is MDS going, then
show everyone so that there is no kitchen sinking
and if you look at the numbers, in whatever way you
see the provision numbers,
they have not come much, those numbers are on growth
only, Aarohi is still at 2%, loan growth was 22%,
wide wise it was just 4%
cotton, so you have nationally results of
very good, I think who is there today and
who will get more clarity after that
because you sir, still many people will have
many questions, whose clarity will be found in that,
respect wise, if we talk about companies, sir,
as I said, banks are doing very well,
Bank of Maharashtra's numbers have come,
very good numbers have come and small companies,
wherever you go, from commodity to oil,
then Hera Maharashtra has
increased this time  So I don't know whether the
run rate is continuous or not, then the
numbers will look very good but they are good in
terms of cotton, cotton
improvement which I think
cotton improvement was 7 basis points, if we
talk about RPG, sir, then domestic companies are
doing very well, 20% up, 10 segmental
international population 26% which was up,
margins are up 52, so this is a good thing, you
know in terms of your G, so in farmer also there are
some domestic companies whose numbers are
good, you Jindal training, as
I told you, it happens in a lot of time,
whatever business comes,
Jindal feeling, so nothing was
very important because it had gone up three times, so I will give
you the numbers, I will give
you the message improvement in this company,
so date, in financial NBFC,
AMFI, in which the report has been given, so these are all
good results, where the company has performed strongly,
tell me the list of weak fishes in use, inside
cement, the whole means SSC, hindal bar,
still cement numbers are weak, I think  By
increasing the ACC number, your cost had
increased a lot, if you see beta button,
₹95% was falling,
46% is cotton, beta cotton had fallen, if I
compare it with Shree Cement,
its 35% is beta button, so I think
even before the results, we had talked about
cement will not be great and
all of them have already fallen, so this was there in it,
but you know, it is about
Tajuddin, sir, today in the morning I was reading everyone's
report,
from all the doctors, so in my opinion, no one else has
cut a very big target
that there will be a rebound in the next quarter, there is another
shooting company, sir, Tata Coffee is
under pressure, this time
analysis to reach us and I
will meet you again tomorrow morning.